

Ngo Buu Anh Duy

Web Developer BirthDay: 10-04-1993 Phone: (+84) 969 652 651

Email:nbaduy104@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://nbaduy-cv.netlify.app/

SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer with 1 years of experience in building web application with good knowledge of VueJS, ReactJS.

I love learning new technologies and building valuable application that helps others with their work. I'm considered a team-player because I like to help other and tend to work well within the group.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- C#, OOP

Frameworks / Platforms:

- VueJS, ReactJS, jQuery
- .Net, NodeJs
- Redux, Mobx
- Element-ui, Material-ui, Bootstrap, Styledcomponent

Foreign Languages:

- English
- Version Control:
 - Git
- Soft Skills:
 - Teamwork
 - Technical communication
 - Highly adaptable

Others:

- Easy to approach, adaptable to new environment
- Hard-working, listening and persevering
- Can read Document and Requirements fast and efficiently
- Always has an urge in researching and learning efficient ways to approach the problems.

EXPERIENCE

Company: One ICC Viet Nam March 2021 – Now

July 2021 - Now:

Project: An Sinh SystemPosition: Web Developer

- **Description:** A system of government funded services and payments to help support the needy circumstances including illness, injury, childbirth, disablement, death, old age...
- Technologies Used: VueJS, Element-ui, NodeJS, MongoDB

- Team Size: 7

March 2021 - July 2021:

- Project: Distribution Management System DMS
- Position: Web Developer
- Description: A Distribution Management System (DMS) is a collection of applications designed to monitor & control the entire distribution network efficiently and reliably
- Technologies Used: VueJS, Element-ui, .Net, MySQL

- Team Size: 7

Personal:

October 2020 – January 2021:

- **Project**: Booking Movie
- Link GitHub: https://github.com/nbduy104/movieproject2021
- Link Demo: https://movieproject-cv.netlify.app/
- Position: Front-end Developer
- **Description:** A online movie tickets booking website with functions: Themes mode, booking tickets, show times, sign up, sign in, change user information
- **Technologies Used:** ReactJS, Material-ui, Styled-component, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- Team Size: 3

EDUCATION

Cybersoft - Cyberlearn Programing Education Center 04/2020 - 01/2021

- Font end course: Basic knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SCSS, JS(ES5/ES6), Git, ReactJS
- Programming course: thinking in programming, problem-solving, Java language, OOP

Bach Khoa University

2011 - 2016

- Major: Automation and Control